cqwen.com 2006-11-30

# My Way - Privacy Policy

Effective Date: July 25, 2005.

**Our Promise To You**  
We do not sell, rent or trade any personally identifiable information ("PII") you provide when using My Way.

**Information We Collect**  
This website and related services ("My Way" or "Site") is owned by My Way, Inc. ("we" or "us"). We do not collect any PII about our users ("you") (such as your name or email address) when you use My Way unless you specifically decide to provide such information in order to enhance your My Way experience. If you choose to provide an email address as part of personalizing My Way, we will not send an email to you unless you specifically request an email response to a customer service inquiry or contact is required in order to protect someone's safety or to enforce our Terms of Service. You are not required to provide an email address to personalize My Way.

We do collect anonymous or non-PII about you in connection with your use of the Site. For example, each time you come to My Way, we collect the limited information that your browser makes available whenever you visit any website: including (a) your Internet Protocol (IP) address, (b) your domain (e.g., whether you logged on from compaq.com or whitehouse.gov), (c) the address of the last URL you visited prior to clicking through to the Site (d) your browser and platform type (e.g., a Netscape browser on a Macintosh platform), (e) your browser language, and (f) the data in any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted from us.

In addition, we, our agents and our commerce partners may use cookies, "pixel tags," "clear GIFs" or other tracking technologies in connection with the Site. For example, when you visit My Way, we place a small text file -- called a "cookie" -- on your computer that allows us to identify your web browser. Cookies and other technologies are used on our site to assist us in understanding aggregate usage of the different areas of our service in order to improve the quality of our service. We also capture your source IP address which is a standard practice for most web sites. We in no way associate cookie and IP address data and also do not use IP address data in conjunction with any personally identifiable information. Cookies and other technologies are also used to customize the service based upon what site you arrived from and to store your preferences and settings.

We note that information collected by our commerce partners will be subject to their privacy policies, not this Privacy Policy.

**Our Use of Information**  
Again, we do not sell, rent or trade any PII you provide when using My Way.

We may use your e-mail for non-marketing purposes, such as: to respond to a request from you; for administrative purposes (such as to notify you of an impending closing of any account that is believed to be abandoned); if we believe we are compelled or otherwise required to do so under applicable law or as part of a legal proceeding; to cooperate with law enforcement or government request; to help protect someone's safety or property; to protect the integrity of the Site; or if there has been a violation or suspected violation of our Terms of Service or Privacy Policy.

Further, if My Way is ever sold or all or substantially all of the assets relating to My Way are transferred to another entity, we may transfer to such acquiring entity the information you have provided to us so as to ensure continuity of your personalized service.

In addition, we may use and disclose anonymous or non-PII, such as aggregated information and statistics regarding Site usage and demographics, for marketing and non-marketing purposes.

**Co-Branded Pages**  
We also offer you access to "co-branded" services that are jointly provided by us and our content providers. In certain cases, services on this Site will contain My Way branding, but might not be hosted by us. You should follow the privacy link on the page to determine which company's privacy policy protects the information you enter on the page.

**Children**  
We do not knowingly collect PII from anyone under the age of 13 without parental consent or otherwise in compliance with applicable law.

**Reviewing Your Personally Identifiable Information**  
To review, revise or delete the personally identifiable information that we have collected about you online that we maintain, please log in to your profile and edit accordingly. You may access your profile [here](http://registration.myway.com/member_info.jsp). However, please understand that although this information, once deleted, is not available on the Site, that information may remain stored indefinitely in our backup and archival records.

**Privacy Policy Updates**  
We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting an updated Privacy Policy on the Site. We ask that you periodically review this page. You may refer to the "Effective Date" at the top of this document to determine when this Privacy Policy was last updated.

My Way, Inc. is a division of IAC Search & Media. Internet privacy is an issue that we take very seriously. We provide this Privacy Policy so that our users will know what personally identifiable information is and is not being collected about you through the Site, how that information is and is not being used, and with whom it is and is not being shared.

Also, although we and our affiliates own or operate other websites, such websites are not governed by this Privacy Policy.
